{"points": {"graphics": 25}, "answers": {"4aa35401d4387958e64116166dce1862f366952f": {"answer": "t", "points": 2, "pset": "graphics"}, "499a7db04c373ff67e6a230f23551aa6563ff486": {"answer": "^subtractive( color mixing)?$", "points": 1, "pset": "graphics"}, "4858daf9936d00e723114ca24980c5f80d6368ca": {"answer": "d", "points": 2, "pset": "graphics"}, "11b6322a771a9d76f8415ceeed14e60f7d806346": {"answer": "^additive( color mixing)?$", "points": 1, "pset": "graphics"}, "16e1f5e23941da96466b4039bba69711521db538": {"answer": "^additive( color mixing)?$", "points": 1, "pset": "graphics"}, "801e5945a97c8356e86ed03c5fa88b05401a4106": {"answer": "^subtractive( color mixing)?$", "points": 1, "pset": "graphics"}, "5d3711c674564de5726e4734f5b13d4654165eca": {"answer": "c", "points": 3, "pset": "graphics"}, "c2c42be3e390a14cbc8cacf268da6f8a8bd3c5c0": {"answer": "Bitmap is a raster graphics format, so images are represented using a grid of pixels, where each pixel has a color composed of values for red, green, and blue.", "points": 1, "pset": "graphics"}, "0eb5e91008c9329cacf7541d602d3462f207934f": {"answer": "f", "points": 2, "pset": "graphics"}, "26d75e8f79bc43af6ddc268ced9bbd9c575c202c": {"answer": "d", "points": 1, "pset": "graphics"}, "f7fd20c32e874d795475e28f08549a64e2f99880": {"answer": "a", "points": 2, "pset": "graphics"}, "26ad847405eb69f6d344c8ca97974245ac46bc9d": {"answer": "f", "points": 2, "pset": "graphics"}, "7e65ca57b5e5732a55fbe054d2ab7fc270230dff": {"answer": "b", "points": 1, "pset": "graphics"}, "7e4c050a989db06003cc8eeeba762248ad7b2ed9": {"answer": "^1([ -]bit)?$", "points": 3, "pset": "graphics"}, "179a88ce8f0b468d9a75c39d4a72a371a5a8d20d": {"answer": "c", "points": 1, "pset": "graphics"}, "96f4d99477168b73fcb7be8cc652061987d24de3": {"answer": "^additive( color mixing)?$", "points": 1, "pset": "graphics"}}, "questions": {"graphics": [{"points": 2, "link": "graphics/file-formats", "answer": "f", "type": "tf", "explanation": "A file's extension is simply a hint to help the operating system determine which program should be used to open the file by default. A file's extension doesn't affect its contents in any way, so a file without an extension can still be opened by a program.", "question": "A file needs to have an extension to be opened.", "id": "0eb5e91008c9329cacf7541d602d3462f207934f"}, {"points": 3, "link": "graphics/file-formats", "answer": "c", "type": "mc", "explanation": "Changing a file's extension does not change a file's format. The \".pdf\" extension simply informs the operating system that a PDF viewer should be used to open the file, but because the file is still in Microsoft Word's format, the PDF viewer won't understand how to display its contents.", "question": "A co-worker sent me a Word document, but I don't have Word on my computer, so I changed the file extension to \".pdf\", since I know my computer can read those. Which of the following best describes what will happen when I double-click the file to open it?", "id": "5d3711c674564de5726e4734f5b13d4654165eca", "choices": {"a": "My computer will not allow me to change a file's extension.", "c": "My PDF viewer will open, but it will not be able to display the contents of the file.", "b": "The contents of the file will correctly be displayed by my PDF viewer.", "d": "My PDF view will not open, and I'll see some kind of error message from the operating system."}}, {"points": 2, "link": "graphics/colors", "answer": "a", "type": "mc", "explanation": "The \"M\" in CMYK stands for \"magenta\". The \"K\" in CMYK stands for \"key\", which refers to black.", "question": "Which of the following is not a primary color in the CMYK color scheme?", "id": "f7fd20c32e874d795475e28f08549a64e2f99880", "choices": {"a": "Maroon", "c": "Yellow", "b": "Black", "d": "Cyan"}}, {"text": "Let's talk about colors! Fill in each of the below with \"additive\" or \"subtractive\".", "type": "sequence", "questions": [{"points": 1, "link": "graphics/colors", "answer": "^additive( color mixing)?$", "type": "fill", "explanation": "Using additive mixing, red, green, and blue light can be used to produce any color.", "question": "Which type of color mixing expresses colors in terms of RGB?", "id": "96f4d99477168b73fcb7be8cc652061987d24de3"}, {"points": 1, "link": "graphics/colors", "answer": "^subtractive( color mixing)?$", "type": "fill", "explanation": "Using subtractive mixing, cyan, magenta, yellow, and key ink can be used to produce any color.", "question": "Which type of color mixing expresses colors in terms of CMYK?", "id": "499a7db04c373ff67e6a230f23551aa6563ff486"}, {"points": 1, "link": "graphics/colors", "answer": "^subtractive( color mixing)?$", "type": "fill", "explanation": "Because we view printed graphics under (white) light, CMYK can be used to absorb some of the light to produce different colors.", "question": "Which type of color mixing is used when printing graphics on paper?", "id": "801e5945a97c8356e86ed03c5fa88b05401a4106"}, {"points": 1, "link": "graphics/colors", "answer": "^additive( color mixing)?$", "type": "fill", "explanation": "Because LCDs shine light into darkness, RGB can be used to add colors together to produce different colors.", "question": "Which type of color mixing is used by the LCDs in your computer's display?", "id": "16e1f5e23941da96466b4039bba69711521db538"}, {"points": 1, "link": "graphics/colors", "answer": "^additive( color mixing)?$", "type": "fill", "explanation": "Typically, hexadecimal color notation uses two digits for red, two for green, and two for blue, in that order.", "question": "When expressing colors using hexadecimal notation, the primary colors of which type of color mixing are used?", "id": "11b6322a771a9d76f8415ceeed14e60f7d806346"}]}, {"points": 3, "link": "graphics/colors", "answer": "^1([ -]bit)?$", "type": "fill", "explanation": "We can represent the color black with the number 0 and the color white with the number 1, so we need only one bit per pixel in order to fully represent a monochrome image.", "question": "What is the color depth of a monochrome, black-and-white image?", "id": "7e4c050a989db06003cc8eeeba762248ad7b2ed9"}, {"text": "Let's review how bitmaps represent images.", "type": "sequence", "questions": [{"points": 1, "link": "graphics/bitmap", "answer": "b", "type": "mc", "explanation": "The beginning of every bitmap file is 0x42 0x4D, or \"BM\" in ASCII. We call these \"magic numbers\" because they signify the start of a bitmap file.", "question": "What is found at the very beginning of a bitmap file?", "id": "7e65ca57b5e5732a55fbe054d2ab7fc270230dff", "choices": {"a": "The color of the first pixel of the image", "c": "Metadata about the image", "b": "A magic number", "d": "How many pixels the bitmap will contain"}}, {"points": 1, "link": "graphics/bitmap", "answer": "d", "type": "mc", "explanation": "The bitmap's metadata includes the image's width, height, color depth, size (in bytes), and resolution, among other things. While other formats may store information about cameras, bitmap does not.", "question": "After the magic number comes the bitmap's metadata. Which of the following is <b>not</b> typically found in a bitmap's metadata section?", "id": "26d75e8f79bc43af6ddc268ced9bbd9c575c202c", "choices": {"a": "The image's width", "c": "The size of the image, in bytes", "b": "The image's color depth", "d": "The type of camera used to capture the image"}}, {"points": 1, "link": "graphics/bitmap", "answer": "Bitmap is a raster graphics format, so images are represented using a grid of pixels, where each pixel has a color composed of values for red, green, and blue.", "type": "mc", "question": "Next up is the actual image data. Which of the following is <b>not</b> true of how images are represented in the bitmap format?", "id": "c2c42be3e390a14cbc8cacf268da6f8a8bd3c5c0", "choices": {"a": "The pixels in the first column are stored first, followed by the second column, and so on.", "c": "Each pixel is represented using the same amount of data.", "b": "Image data is represented using 0s and 1s.", "d": "Bitmaps are a raster graphics format."}}, {"points": 1, "link": "graphics/bitmap", "answer": "c", "type": "mc", "explanation": "Each pixel is represented using 24 bits, so 8 bits are dedicated to each of red, green, and blue.", "question": "For a 24-bit bitmap, which of the following values could represent a single pixel?", "id": "179a88ce8f0b468d9a75c39d4a72a371a5a8d20d", "choices": {"a": "#aaddgg", "c": "#c0ffee", "b": "#abcd", "d": "#123"}}]}, {"points": 2, "link": "graphics/lossless-compression", "answer": "f", "type": "tf", "explanation": "Lossless compression algorithms preserve all of the file's original data.", "question": "Because GIF is a lossless format, data may be lost in the compression process.", "id": "26ad847405eb69f6d344c8ca97974245ac46bc9d"}, {"points": 2, "link": "graphics/lossy-compression", "answer": "t", "type": "tf", "explanation": "Many digital photos are stored as compressed JPEGs.", "question": "Although lossy compression formats like JPEG throw away some of the file's original data, differences in the compressed file are difficult to detect, even for high compression ratios.", "id": "4aa35401d4387958e64116166dce1862f366952f"}, {"points": 2, "link": "graphics/vector-graphics", "answer": "d", "type": "mc", "explanation": "SVG, or scalable vector graphics, uses mathematical equations to describe the shapes composing the image.", "question": "Which of the following best describes how vector graphics are represented?", "id": "4858daf9936d00e723114ca24980c5f80d6368ca", "choices": {"a": "With a grid of pixels, where each pixel has an associated color", "c": "With a set of polygons and positions of those polygons", "b": "With a list of colors and the number of consecutive pixels with that color", "d": "With equations describing shapes and lines, like x^2 + y^2 = r^2"}}, {"question": "Try seam carving some of your own photos! It's really cool. Content-aware scaling is available in both Photoshop and as a plugin for the GIMP, but you can also just download the Seam Carving GUI. Images with lots of empty space in the horizontal or vertical directions will produce the best results!", "link": "graphics/seam-carving", "id": "720d195695ee6751233fedc2bef176e2e5c1acd1", "type": "try"}]}}